

NAZMUL HAQUE SAJOL **WORDPRESS DEVELOPER**

PROFILE

Versatile Front-End Developer with 5+ years of experience designing, developing and managing complex sites including e-Commerce as well as internal frameworks. Specializes in WordPress and responsive design. With a keen eye on design, I leverage Front-End latest tech to build interactive features and website that drive business growth and improve UX. I'm seeking position in a top technology firm with challenging projects.

PRO SKILLS

DESIGN HTML/CSS **JAVASCRIPT** WORDPRESS DEVOPS

PROJECTS



LANGUAGE

BENGALI NATIVE **ENGLISH FLUENT**

HINDI CONVERSATIONAL

INTERESTS

TRAVELING CYCLEING **GUITAR** FILM MAKING SPACE TECH **MEDITATION**

OHAKA, BANGLADESH

+880 1787332124

NHSAJOLBD@GMAIL.COM

WORK EXPERIENCE

WORDPRESS DEVELOPER Upwork -APR 2020 - PRESENT

Working as a Top Rated WordPress freelancer for almost five years. In the meantime, I successfully worked on 20+ projects, 500+ hours, and received satisfactory feedback.

FRONT-END DEVELOPER SEPT 2019 - OCT 2020 JARVIS DIGITAL Dhaka, Bangl

A creative agency based in Dhaka, specializing in bringing brands to the online space with our expertise in digital strategies and graphical & technical superpowers!

FRONT-END DEVELOPER MAY 2019 - OCT 2019

TONIX.

A full service digital solutions agency that provides digital consultancy to build an effective solutions for your business and customers

FRONT-END DEVELOPER FEB 2017 - FEB 2019 TECHTONIX Dhaka, Bangla

Digital Agency based on Abu Dhabi, UAE. Building custom WordPress website and front-end support for various application is my core responsibility.

EDUCATION



CERTIFICATION

IT PASSPORT EXAM (IP) INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY ENGINEERS EXAMINATION (ITEE) FEB 2018 A national level IT Engineers Examination governed by IPA, Japan **WEB DEVELOPMENT** CODERSTRUST BANGLADESH OCT 2015 A company that is changing the way freelancers learn and earn.

MY STACKS



REFERENCE

MOHAMED NAEEM

Business Development - Tonix

Phone: +971-50-721-0066 Email: mohamed@tonix.agency ABDULLAH BAKR

CEO - Jarvis Digital

Phone: 01707-662796

Email: abdullahbakr@jarvisdigitalbd.com